ACWA's Union Label Department Records 5619/039
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Leo Arnoult, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Jim Anderson, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Jeff Ballinger, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Harlen Baker Portland, ME, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Jeff Ballinger, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Father Donald Dauer, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Henry Becker, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Henry T. Becker, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Benton Bell, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Benton Bell Louisville, Kentucky, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Sarah Broom, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Bernadine Bryant Minn., 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Ed Burns, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Frank Booth Byers (Red), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Stan Clair, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- James Cleary, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Fr. Clifford, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Corcoran, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Bill Cross Birmingham, Ala., 1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- John Cummingham, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Nick D'Andrea, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Bernard Dinkin, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Tony Du Charme (N.Y. State), 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Edmond Dolliole and John Cunningham - New Orleans, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Sharron L. Farrell, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Reuben Fishman, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Jean Garner, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Edith Gero, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- HY Goldberg, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Goldstein J.L Hudson Detroit, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Pete Goldstein, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Fred Goldberg (Central States), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Gundersheim, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Bob Harbrant, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Rev. Larry Kennon, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Arthur Keys, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Jerry Landman, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Landman, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- L. Lewis, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Gaetan Joseph LePage, Jr., 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Rev. H. Ralph Jackson, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Louise Majors, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Ruth Miller[folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Ruth Miller [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Harold Wyss (Wisconsin), 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Pam Woywod, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Milton Watson (Georgia), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Milton Watson, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Hattie Williams, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Wiseman, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Louise Witt (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Robert Wiseman, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Stocco, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Rev. Middlebrook, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Victor Mills, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Emileo Molleda, Jr. Smithfield, Texas, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Leslie Anne Nader, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- O' Donovan, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- George Nejmeh, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Bobby Lee Parrish Montgomery, Ala., 1973 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Elvin Stewart, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Watson, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Opal Stingley, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Phil Stocco, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Jim Trulock, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Joe Pastore, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Bill Paterson, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Knuti Van Hoven - San Francisco, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Rev. Joel Strauch Union Theological Seminary, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- James Tribble, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Calvin Sosby, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Cleron Smith, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- Louis Shipman, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- Shipman [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Shipman [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Wyss, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Oscar Sanchez, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Patrick Joseph Smyth, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Nicholas Reale, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Virginia Perry, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Wilma Robertson, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- W. Louise Robertson, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  February 4
- Raymond F. Rogers, Jr., 1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Smith (Cleron-Buster), 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Father Bauer Special Mailing list (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Fr. Bauer - religious contacts coast-to-coast, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- FARAH Boycott Action report of religious participation, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  May
- Akron, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Albany, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Albuquerque, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Allentown, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Atlanta, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Austin, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Baltimore, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Boston, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Buffalo, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Charleston, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Chicago, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Cincinnati, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Cleveland, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Columbus, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Detroit, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Davenport, Iowa, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- El Paso, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Erie, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Green Bay, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  July 24
- Greensburg, Pa., 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Hartford, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Harrisburg, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Indianapolis, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Jefferson City, Mo., 1973 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Kansas City, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Knoxville, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Little Rock, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Los Angeles, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Louisville, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Memphis, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Madison, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Milwaukee, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Minneapolis, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Mobile, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  March 9
- Nashville, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Newark, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- New Haven, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- New Orleans, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Catholic Lists - requests for flyers FARAH film Catholic Schools, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Father Bauer letters, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- San Antonio, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- San Francisco, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 56)
- Seattle, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Springfield, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- St. Louis, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 59)
- Syracuse, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 60)
- Toledo, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 61)
- Washington, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 62)
- Youngstown, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 63)
- NYC, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 64)
- Philadelphia, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 65)
- Pittsburgh, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 66)
- Portland, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 67)
- Rochester, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 68)
- "Religious packet" Mailed to clergy, etc. requesting info, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 69)
- Fr. Bauer letters to Catholic hierarchy, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  August 9
- Letter to Catholic Schools, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 71)
- Fr. Bauer - Photos of Bishop Metzger (Box 12, Folder 72)
- Caravan, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  February 20
- Requests for brochures, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  October 24
- Copies of instructions on running film (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Showing of film, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  October 10
- Originals of Memo's, forms, etc. (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Follow up on Areas not showing film (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Copies of Memo to: Joint Board. Managers (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Copies of memo to: organizations and individuals using general office prints in N.Y. (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Supply/ film orders, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous. film showing correspondence, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous. Correspondence, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Fr. Bauer- Critique of Rev. Poling's position (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Interoffice, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Staff Conferences, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- El Paso Preliminary luncheon (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Requests for showings referred to field, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Weekly summaries of report of film showings, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Reply (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Billboards, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- ADA -Van Heusen, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Van Heusen Boycott newsletters - blank copies (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Phillip Van Heusen Misc., 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Van Heusen Boycott News- Headlines legally approved, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Van Heusen Boycott newsletters not used, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Van Heusen Boycott news - general correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Van Heusen Boycott News, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Van Heusen Budget, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Father Bauer, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Burt Beck (Re. Van Heusen), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Clergy contacts, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  June 11
- Religious (Van Heusen), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  May 9
- Publicity/clippings, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Crank letters, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- D.N.R., 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Fact Sheet, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Fact Sheet Requests, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- VH Film and leaflet mailings ("so long,…"), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Film, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Finance (Re. Van Heusen), 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Del V.H., 1975 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- "Hypocrisy" AD (ADA Journal), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Van Heusen Labor Record requests, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Labor Press, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Van Heusen - Leaflets, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Profit vs. Social justice response, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Van Heusen - Legal, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Letters - consumers, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  June 20
- Letters to retailers, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Letters from VH, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Labor Letters, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Logan Valley (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Maurer Fleisher and Zon and Anderson, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- HDS Memo, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Inter-office memo, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Mintzer Green, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Van Heusen Mintzer-Trostler Bills, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- NLRB, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Notes and minutes on Van Heusen meetings, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  November 4
- Picketing, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  December 11 and 19
- (Van Heusen) Press Release, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Van Heusen Propaganda, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Radio, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Van Heusen Labor record (rebuttal), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  April
- Van Heusen- reports, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  April 22
- Resolutions, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Shopping centers, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Situation Report, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Jim Anderson, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Harlan Baker, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Sarah Broom, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Bernadine Bryant, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  July 15
- Frank Bryers (red), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  March 21
- Stan Clair, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Jack Corcoran, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Bob Gaw (Box 14, Folder 35)
- HY Goldberg, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Pete Goldstein, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Hector Gonzalez, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- B. Justice, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Arthur Keys, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Jerry Landman, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Emileo Molleda, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Paul Mignini, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- Leslie Anne Nader, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Bill Patterson, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Ray Rogers, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- Schmitz, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- Alice Senturia, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 48)
- Cleron Smith, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 49)
- Rev. Melvin Chester Swann African waters methodist church, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 50)
- Phil Stocco, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  July 31
- Robert Wiseman, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- Retail mailing, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  August 19
- Staff Mailing, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  From January
- Van Heusen. Staff Mailing, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Van Heusen - Staff Meetings, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- General strike support- retail campaign, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Van Heusen - Targets, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Telephone, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Van Heusen -Citizen Committee, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- "We the people" AD, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- We the people- Birmingham Post-Herald, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- We the people -Boston Globe, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- We the people -Chicago Sun-Times, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- We the people - Cleveland The Plain Dealer, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- We the people - Detroit Free Press, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- We the people -New York, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- We the people -Philadelphia Inquirer, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- We the people -St. Louis St. Louis Post-Dispatch, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- United Garment Workers, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- White Papers, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  leafleting time cards